hi I'm Bonnie and I'm recording this
from the studio at all the Lord insight
center today I want to talk a little bit
about why we've created this summer
program for young adults at all the
lower soul I've been working with adults
for over 30 years in professional and
community organizations as a coach as an
educator as a spiritual teacher and I've
been writing philosophy on integral
process philosophy for many many years
and the trajectory that I've been
working with is being able to make
explicit new ways of being new ways of
thinking new ways of creating insight
new capacities of cognition and
consciousness and one of the
difficulties that always comes up either
an individual or group basis is the need
to deconstruct or dismantle or
disentangle the old ways of being the
old structures the way that we've grown
up in the world the old world and the
social structures and the individual
structures of the self the way they've
been kind of coagulated and contracted
and built up as layers and really limit
our ability to work directly with our
inner knowing or intuition and as I've
been doing this work for a long time and
grown up with my own colleagues and
community our own children have become
older and gone off to college and it
occurred to us that they were in the
same situation that we were in many many
years ago that they were they still had
the enthusiasm for the new but they were
entering really the same types of
institutionalized education the same
types of institutionalized careers were
ahead of them and that it became very
frustrating to see now that we have
finally done all this work on ourselves
and opened ourselves
to new ways of being that we were seeing
this generations being put through the
same standardized institutionalized
socialized conventionalized static boxes
and we thought well you know why should
young people who don't yet have these
limiting structures go through all that
and just in order to have their family
their career and then at an older
midlife crisis age sit down and groups
like we were working with to deconstruct
all that so I started doing a little
research I started doing presentations
for example where young people would
come in and I would organize the
presentations in an interactive way and
experiment and sure enough i found that
young people had a natural intuition for
thinking in new terms for thinking in
more participatory ways for thinking in
open and insightful ways for
acknowledging a deeper spirituality a
deeper kind of inner knowing and
intuition and this really gave me the
incentive to work toward gathering and
assembling and working with the younger
people so last year at one of these
workshops I met Zach schlosser and after
the workshop we really started talking
about working together and building a
program that could create synergy
amongst young people who deep inside
know that the the experiences that they
are having in conventional social
programs is limiting them that they
don't get an affirmation for what they
can see is real in their future a real
possibility real potential in the future
you know I like to do workshops with
young people will where I come in I say
something in you wants to move and my
job is to facilitate that movement and
and that movement has its own natural
genius and natural intelligence and so
for this generation I feel that there's
many of you out there who can feel this
inside themselves that in this time of
rapid change and deinstitutionalization
and decentralization and distributed
agency that there's a real opportunity
for natural leaders to step forward and
recreate recreate the generative
structures that will bring in the new so
that we can make a leap and overcome
some of these situational problems some
of these structures that people in many
many generations before you have had to
really work hard to dismantle at many
stages of their lives so I think this is
a is a unique and historic epochal
opportunity to gather the right people
to find out who we are to assemble these
natural born leaders to work to be able
to work directly with our inner knowing
to make that that's late in and implicit
and not well defined make that to be
explicit to be open and available to
everyone of your generation and
generations to come and so that what is
calling but is what is calling forth
what is being shaped in US and through
us can become an actual realization and
really propel us into the future that we
want to see so many many many people of
your generations of these younger
generations want to make a positive
contribution in world want to make their
life an authentic life well worth living
they want to help others they want to be
in service
they can see that possibility so closely
they can taste it but the structures
aren't there the paths haven't been laid
out and this is what we want to do in
this first small step at the summer
school at all the Lord to really start
to create this community of leaders that
can really look into the future and see
the extraordinary possibility that is
being called from these younger
generations that have this implicit
understanding of the world that is
possible that has never been possible
before so I really hope to meet you and
I hope to see you here this summer at
all the Lord thanks for watching